{
    "success": true,
    "errorMessage": "",
    "quiz": [
        {
            "id": "61d53a86f59118536a17f19d",
            "code": 1405,
            "question": "What age are you?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "id": "61d53b00f59118536a17f1a0",
                    "answer": "Under 30 years",
                    "weightage": 0.1,
                    "question": "61d53a86f59118536a17f19d",
                    "order": 1
                },
                {
                    "id": "61d53b00f59118536a17f1a1",
                    "answer": "31 to 39 years",
                    "weightage": 0.2,
                    "question": "61d53a86f59118536a17f19d",
                    "order": 2
                },
                {
                    "id": "61d53b00f59118536a17f1a2",
                    "answer": "40 to 50 years",
                    "weightage": 0.3,
                    "question": "61d53a86f59118536a17f19d",
                    "order": 3
                },
                {
                    "id": "61d53b00f59118536a17f1a3",
                    "answer": "Over 50 years",
                    "weightage": 0.4,
                    "question": "61d53a86f59118536a17f19d",
                    "order": 4
                }
            ],
            "weightage": 0.1,
            "inActive": false,
            "order": 1
        },
        {
            "id": "61023b141e85f8728c3428be",
            "code": 1655,
            "question": "How long have you been investing?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "id": "61023b141e85f8728c3428bf",
                    "answer": "Never invested",
                    "weightage": 0.8,
                    "question": "61023b141e85f8728c3428be",
                    "order": 1
                },
                {
                    "id": "61023b141e85f8728c3428c0",
                    "answer": "1 to 3 years",
                    "weightage": 0.3,
                    "question": "61023b141e85f8728c3428be",
                    "order": 2
                },
                {
                    "id": "61023b141e85f8728c3428c1",
                    "answer": "4 to 7 years",
                    "weightage": 0.2,
                    "question": "61023b141e85f8728c3428be",
                    "order": 3
                },
                {
                    "id": "61023b141e85f8728c3428c2",
                    "answer": "\u003e7 years",
                    "weightage": 0.1,
                    "question": "61023b141e85f8728c3428be",
                    "order": 4
                }
            ],
            "weightage": 0.1,
            "inActive": false,
            "order": 2
        },
        {
            "id": "61caacc9ac772b90338e6f20",
            "code": 1620,
            "question": "What are your current investments?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "id": "61caaf8af59118536a17f181",
                    "answer": "Mutual Funds",
                    "weightage": 0,
                    "question": "61caacc9ac772b90338e6f20",
                    "order": 1
                },
                {
                    "id": "61caaf8af59118536a17f182",
                    "answer": "Physical Gold",
                    "weightage": 0,
                    "question": "61caacc9ac772b90338e6f20",
                    "order": 2
                },
                {
                    "id": "61caaf8af59118536a17f183",
                    "answer": "Direct Stocks",
                    "weightage": 0,
                    "question": "61caacc9ac772b90338e6f20",
                    "order": 3
                },
                {
                    "id": "61caaf8af59118536a17f184",
                    "answer": "Crypto",
                    "weightage": 0,
                    "question": "61caacc9ac772b90338e6f20",
                    "order": 4
                },
                {
                    "id": "61caaf8af59118536a17f185",
                    "answer": "Real Estate",
                    "weightage": 0,
                    "question": "61caacc9ac772b90338e6f20",
                    "order": 5
                },
                {
                    "id": "61caaf8af59118536a17f186",
                    "answer": "Bonds",
                    "weightage": 0,
                    "question": "61caacc9ac772b90338e6f20",
                    "order": 6
                },
                {
                    "id": "61caaf8af59118536a17f187",
                    "answer": "PMS/AIF",
                    "weightage": 0,
                    "question": "61caacc9ac772b90338e6f20",
                    "order": 7
                },
                {
                    "id": "61caaf8af59118536a17f188",
                    "answer": "Fixed Deposits",
                    "weightage": 0,
                    "question": "61caacc9ac772b90338e6f20",
                    "order": 8
                },
                {
                    "id": "61caaf8af59118536a17f189",
                    "answer": "P2P Lending",
                    "weightage": 0,
                    "question": "61caacc9ac772b90338e6f20",
                    "order": 9
                },
                {
                    "id": "61caaf8af59118536a17f18a",
                    "answer": "Unlisted Equity",
                    "weightage": 0,
                    "question": "61caacc9ac772b90338e6f20",
                    "order": 10
                },
                {
                    "id": "61d82517f77bdbfca1731513",
                    "answer": "Futures \u0026 Options",
                    "weightage": 0,
                    "question": "61caacc9ac772b90338e6f20",
                    "order": 11
                }
            ],
            "multiSelect": true,
            "weightage": 0,
            "inActive": false,
            "order": 3
        },
        {
            "id": "61caacfbac772b90338e9a67",
            "code": 1829,
            "question": "How do you currently invest?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "id": "61caafe2f59118536a17f18b",
                    "answer": "On my own",
                    "weightage": 0,
                    "question": "61caacfbac772b90338e9a67",
                    "order": 1
                },
                {
                    "id": "61caafe2f59118536a17f18c",
                    "answer": "I have a certified financial advisor",
                    "weightage": 0,
                    "question": "61caacfbac772b90338e9a67",
                    "order": 2
                },
                {
                    "id": "61caafe2f59118536a17f18d",
                    "answer": "My bank RM helps me",
                    "weightage": 0,
                    "question": "61caacfbac772b90338e9a67",
                    "order": 3
                },
                {
                    "id": "61caafe2f59118536a17f18e",
                    "answer": "My friend/family helps me invest",
                    "weightage": 0,
                    "question": "61caacfbac772b90338e9a67",
                    "order": 4
                }
            ],
            "multiSelect": true,
            "weightage": 0,
            "inActive": false,
            "order": 4
        },
        {
            "id": "61caad22ac772b90338eb8a4",
            "code": 1231,
            "question": "Who depends on you financially?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "id": "61cab21af59118536a17f18f",
                    "answer": "Kid(s)",
                    "weightage": 0.3,
                    "question": "61caad22ac772b90338eb8a4",
                    "order": 1
                },
                {
                    "id": "61cab21af59118536a17f190",
                    "answer": "Spouse",
                    "weightage": 0.3,
                    "question": "61caad22ac772b90338eb8a4",
                    "order": 2
                },
                {
                    "id": "61cab21af59118536a17f191",
                    "answer": "Parents",
                    "weightage": 0.3,
                    "question": "61caad22ac772b90338eb8a4",
                    "order": 3
                },
                {
                    "id": "61cab21af59118536a17f192",
                    "answer": "Other family",
                    "weightage": 0.3,
                    "question": "61caad22ac772b90338eb8a4",
                    "order": 4
                },
                {
                    "id": "61d53c8448442f9610a2a903",
                    "answer": "No dependents",
                    "weightage": 0,
                    "question": "61caad22ac772b90338eb8a4",
                    "order": 5
                }
            ],
            "multiSelect": true,
            "weightage": 0,
            "inActive": false,
            "order": 5
        },
        {
            "id": "61d53bc5f59118536a17f1a4",
            "code": 1809,
            "question": "What temporary drop in your portfolio value would make you lose sleep?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "id": "61d53be4f59118536a17f1a6",
                    "answer": "Canâ€™t handle any drop",
                    "weightage": 4,
                    "question": "61d53bc5f59118536a17f1a4",
                    "order": 1
                },
                {
                    "id": "61d53be4f59118536a17f1a5",
                    "answer": "-5% to -10%",
                    "weightage": 1.5,
                    "question": "61d53bc5f59118536a17f1a4",
                    "order": 2
                },
                {
                    "id": "61d53be4f59118536a17f1a7",
                    "answer": "-11% to -20%",
                    "weightage": 1,
                    "question": "61d53bc5f59118536a17f1a4",
                    "order": 3
                },
                {
                    "id": "61d53be4f59118536a17f1a8",
                    "answer": "\u003e -20%",
                    "weightage": 0.5,
                    "question": "61d53bc5f59118536a17f1a4",
                    "order": 4
                }
            ],
            "weightage": 0.5,
            "inActive": false,
            "order": 6
        },
        {
            "id": "61caad7eac772b9033900810",
            "code": 1808,
            "question": "Are you a salaried professional?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "id": "61cab24bf59118536a17f193",
                    "answer": "Yes",
                    "weightage": 0,
                    "question": "61caad7eac772b9033900810",
                    "order": 1
                },
                {
                    "id": "61cab24bf59118536a17f194",
                    "answer": "No",
                    "weightage": 0,
                    "question": "61caad7eac772b9033900810",
                    "order": 2
                }
            ],
            "weightage": 0,
            "inActive": false,
            "order": 7
        },
        {
            "id": "61caadaaac772b903390eb18",
            "code": 1265,
            "question": "What is your profession?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "id": "61cab292f59118536a17f195",
                    "answer": "Entrepreneur",
                    "weightage": 0,
                    "question": "61caadaaac772b903390eb18",
                    "order": 1
                },
                {
                    "id": "61cab292f59118536a17f196",
                    "answer": "Freelancer",
                    "weightage": 0,
                    "question": "61caadaaac772b903390eb18",
                    "order": 2
                },
                {
                    "id": "61cab292f59118536a17f197",
                    "answer": "Retired",
                    "weightage": 0,
                    "question": "61caadaaac772b903390eb18",
                    "order": 3
                },
                {
                    "id": "61cab292f59118536a17f198",
                    "answer": "Homemaker",
                    "weightage": 0,
                    "question": "61caadaaac772b903390eb18",
                    "order": 4
                },
                {
                    "id": "61d80fb4f77bdbfca13fd146",
                    "answer": "Full-time investor",
                    "weightage": 0,
                    "question": "61caadaaac772b903390eb18",
                    "order": 5
                },
                {
                    "id": "61d80fbdf77bdbfca13ffcd1",
                    "answer": "Other",
                    "weightage": 0,
                    "question": "61caadaaac772b903390eb18",
                    "order": 6
                }
            ],
            "weightage": 0,
            "inActive": false,
            "order": 8
        }
    ]
}